horrornews.net 2019-06-11

# HNN | Privacy Policy - Horrornews.net

HNN ([horrornews.net](https://horrornews.net/)) is committed to protecting its users’ privacy. This Privacy Policy (the “Privacy Policy”), as set forth below, covers [horrornews.net](https://horrornews.net/) (the “Site,”) and applies solely to information collected on [horrornews.net](https://horrornews.net/) Please read this Privacy Policy to understand how we will treat personally and non-personally identifiable information we collect on [horrornews.net](https://horrornews.net/)

We are the sole owners of the information collected on this site. We only have access to/collect information that you voluntarily give us via email or other direct contact from you. We will not sell or rent this information to anyone.

We will use your information to respond to you, regarding the reason you contacted us. We will not share your information with any third party outside of our organization, other than as necessary to fulfill your request, e.g. to ship an order.

We do not share any of your personally identifiable information with third parties outside of [horrornews.net](https://horrornews.net/) without your consent.

**Information We Collect:**  
This notice applies to all information collected or submitted on the Site. On some pages, you can make comments, complete user profiles, complete contest entry forms, register to receive newsletters or other digital messaging. The types of personally identifiable information collected at these pages are at least: Name, Email Address.

We do not share any of your personally identifiable information with third parties outside of [horrornews.net](https://horrornews.net/) without your consent You can give this consent by “opting-in” to having your information shared with third parties when the option is available during your online interaction. These third parties may include our marketing partners, who may want specific information to better shape their marketing efforts. Additionally, we may provide the community the opportunity to choose to be sent newsletters and other information. We will not send this information to you unless you “opt in” for these services and publications.

[Horrornews.net](http://horrornews.net/) will not sell, dispose, or otherwise transfer your personally identifiable information to third parties without your consent except as specifically set forth in this paragraph and in the preceding paragraph.

**How To Contact Us**  
Should you have any questions or concerns about these privacy policies, please send us an email at [news@horrornews.net](mailto:news@horrornews.net)

**Third Party Advertising**  
We use Playwire and other third-party advertising companies to serve ads when you visit our Web site. These companies may use information (not including your name, address, email address or telephone number) about your visits to this and other Web sites in order to provide advertisements on this site and other sites about goods and services that may be of interest to you. I

**Automatically Logged Information:**  
We personally do not collect any information on consumers who browse our Web page

**Advertisers:**  
We currently use several outside ad companies to display ads on our site. These ads may contain cookies (see below). Cookies received with banner ads are collected by the ad companies, and we do not have access to this information. Our site does not use cookies.
